>> So when did people first start to use A/B testing?
人类最初从什么时候开始使用 A/B 测试？
>> A/B testing has been around a long time, maybe we didn't call it
A/B 测试的历史很长 一开始应该是出现在农业领域
A/B testing, but it typically came from field such as agriculture,
虽然那时候还不叫 A/B 测试
where people would actually divide up their land into sections and
人们将土地分为各个部分
then test what would work better for a particular crop or how it grew.
然后测试哪个地方最适合某种作物或者作物如何生长
And so there have been a lot of different fields that use what's
其实有很多不同的领域
effectively A/B testing for a long time.
在很长时间内都在实际使用 A/B 测试
>> In the sciences more generally,
一般来说 在科学领域中
hypotheses testing is a key way that they really determine innovation.
假设检验是确定创新的关键方法
In medicine, for example, their version of A/B testing is called clinical trials
医学上的 A/B 测试称为临床试验
and that's how they determine whether a new drug is effective or not.
他们会藉此确定新药品是否有效
>> The key thing that you want to see in A/B testing is that you have
在 A/B 测试中你最想看到的
a consistent response from your control and your experiment group, so
是对照组和实验组返回一致的响应
that you can actually really determine and structure the experiment, so
让你能够真正地决定试验的结构
you can determine whether there's a significant behavior change in your
确定实验组以及对照组
experiment group as opposed to in your control group.
是否有很明显的行为改变
>> Okay.
好的
So what's the difference between running these types of experiments and
所以运行这些试验以及在线 A/B 测试之间
running online A/B tests?
有什么不同？
>> Well, in the online world we often have a lot more data but
网络上 我们有更多更多的数据
kind of lower resolution.
但是分辨率更低
So in a traditional medical trial or in a user experience research study,
在传统的医学试验或者用户体验研究中
you might have ten, twenty, fifty participants.
你可能有 10 个、20 个或者 50 个参与者
So normally is the analysis different, because you have to be very careful,
所以分析的时候会不同 因为你必须很小心
but you know a lot about each participant in your trial,
但是你很了解试验中的每个参与者
so you may know their age, their weight.
你知道他们的年龄、体重
You know its a single person, you have their drivers license, all this stuff.
你知道他是一个人 有他们的驾驶证 诸如此类
You may have met them, whereas in an online study,
你也可能有见过他们 但是在在线研究中
you may have millions of users, hundreds of thousands of clicks, respondents.
你可能有几百万用户 几十万的点击和应答
But you don't really know that much about who's on the other end
但是你无法真正得知
of that data.
数据的另一端是谁
So, it may be something where you have trouble distinguishing whether this is
你可能很难确认
a single person, whether there's multiple people.
这是一个人 还是几个人
Is it an internet cafe computer?
是不是网咖的电脑？
And those are issues that really come up in online user data.
在在线用户数据中你真的会遇到这些问题
>> The key thing to remember is that in the online world,
网络世界中要谨记的一件事就是
when you're doing A/B testing, the goal really is to determine whether or
当你做 A/B 测试时 目的是要确认
not this new product or this new feature is something that users will like.
用户是否会喜欢这个新产品或新功能
And so the goal in A/B testing is to design an experiment, that's going to be
所以在进行 A/B 测试时 你的目标是
robust and give you repeatable results, so that you can actually make a good
设计一个合理且能够给到你可复验的结果
decision about whether or not to actually launch that product or feature.
让你能够很好地决定是否要发布一款产品或功能
>> Sounds good.
听起来不错
I know Udacity uses A/B testing.
我知道优达学城使用 A/B 测试
How about other tech companies?
其他技术公司呢？
>> It's everywhere right now.
现在它无处不在
Google, Microsoft, eBay, PayPal, Netflix,
Google、Microsoft、eBay、PayPal、Netflix
like all of the major companies are definitely using A/B testing.
基本上所有主要的公司都在使用 A/B 测试
There are even companies that focus on providing those services
甚至还有公司专门为小公司提供这些服务
to smaller companies, like optimizing their sites better.
帮助他们优化网站等等